<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-8046" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">Axe Throwing</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc ">This is my date idea for thrill-seeking couples or those who want a competitive game.</shortdesc><body class="- topic/body "><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">About</title><p class="- topic/p ">Blue Ridge Axe Throwing is the ultimate destination for adrenaline junkies. You will never be bored here, with an arcade, games, pinball, and most importantly: axe throwing! Impress your date by show off your pitching skills.<fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Blue Ridge Axe Throwing Exterior</title><image width="550" href="Photos/blue-ridge-axe1.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">The outside of the Blue Ridge Axe Throwing building, with a large blue sign.</alt></image></fig></p></section><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">Review</title><p class="- topic/p ">A recent addition to Blacksburg, this is one of the most exciting spots in town. I went with a couple of friends when it first opened and had a blast letting off some steam and sharing many laughs. You can walk-in if you're looking for last minute plans or reserve your own space ahead if you want some alone time.</p></section><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">Recommendation</title><p class="- topic/p ">Prepare for a competitive match of axe throwing! There will be a lot of tension in the room – whether it be from your date wanting to kiss you – or their determination to beat you. While Blue Ridge Axe Throwing generally isn't too busy, I recommend calling ahead to schedule your time slot and fill out your waiver to ensure there's no wait.</p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Blue Ridge Axe Throwing Interior</title><image width="400" href="Photos/blue-ridge-axe2.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">A woman in a Blue Ridge Axe Throwing t-shirt is pulling her arm back to prepare her axe throw.</alt></image></fig></section></body></topic>