<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-4765" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">Lyric Theatre</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc ">This is my date idea for dramatic couples or those who want to visit a vintage Blacksburg staple.</shortdesc><body class="- topic/body "><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">About</title><p class="- topic/p ">Built
in Downtown Blacksburg during the roaring 1920s, The Lyric Theatre is a luxurious
historic movie theatre with a large screen, wooden stage, orchestra pit, and
seating for nearly 500 people. </p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">The Lyric Exterior</title><image width="550" href="Photos/the-lyric2.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">The outside of a movie theater that reads the words "LYRIC" in bright yellow lettering on a maroon sign.</alt></image></fig></section><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">Review</title><p class="- topic/p ">I watched the 2023 <varname class="+ topic/keyword sw-d/varname ">Barbie</varname>
movie here. Everything is so much bigger and better here than other movie theaters
– I felt fully immersed in the experience. Plus, knowing I was supporting a
small local business felt sweet. If you choose your dates based on the
ambiance, then this is the place for you.</p></section><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">Recommendation</title><p class="- topic/p ">The Lyric is typically open on weekends but may close early on weekdays without major movies showing, so plan for a weekend visit and check their website for showtimes. During the summer, the theater offers Free Movie Fridays, where they showcase a throwback film with free entry. Grab a large popcorn, strawberry licorice, and a cherry coke for that vintage feeling!</p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">The Lyric Interior</title><image width="550" href="Photos/the-lyric1.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">A large movie theater with a large screen, wooden stage, and orchestra pit.</alt></image></fig></section></body></topic>