<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-8347" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">The Wine Lab</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc ">This is my date idea for couples who love to taste new things or those who want to have a drink without going to a dive bar.</shortdesc><body class="- topic/body "><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">About</title><p class="- topic/p ">If you like to indulge your pallet with many flavors from all over the world without the price and time spent traveling, then The Wine Lab is the perfect date destination for you. True to its name, this chemistry-themed restaurant serves wine in graduated cylinders, adding a fun and quirky touch to your tasting experience.</p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">The Wine Lab Bar</title><image href="Photos/the-wine-lab2.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">A large bar with hundreds of wines and a chandelier overhead.</alt></image></fig></section><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">Review</title><p class="- topic/p ">As a self-proclaimed wine aficionado, I might be a little biased, but The Wine Lab is the best spot in town for drinks. The atmosphere of the "lab" is a unique experience every visit, the food is locally sourced and delicious, and the rotating drink menu features high-quality wines that never disappoint.</p></section><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">Recommendation</title><p class="- topic/p ">A five-minute walk off campus, this restaurant is conveniently located for you and your date to take a beautiful evening stroll around Virginia Tech and Downtown Blacksburg, finishing with a nice meal and a glass (or two) of wine. I recommend visiting on a weeknight when it's less busy with undergraduate students and professors. Start with the dip plate and a soup. If you're like me and love smooth reds, order the Radiant Red Flight; however, if you are unsure which type of wine is more your style, try the Captain's Chair Flight.</p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Captain's Flight and Radiant Red Flight</title><image href="Photos/wine-lab10.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">Six glasses of wine in graduated cylinders.</alt></image></fig></section></body></topic>