<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-6555" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">The Coffee Cauldron</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc ">This is my date idea for laid-back couples or those who want a late-night cozy atmosphere.</shortdesc><body class="- topic/body "><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">About</title><p class="- topic/p ">A cute spooky-themed café, The Coffee Cauldron is the newest coffee spot on the block. While it sells the classics – coffee, hot chocolate, and pastries – it stands out with its late-night hours! Plan on staying up late to get all your fun activities done while you're in town? The Coffee Cauldron's espresso will be sure to keep you up!</p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Halloween Cookies at Coffee Cauldron</title><image href="Photos/coffee-cauldron9.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">A orange pumpkin sugar cookie and a purple bat sugar cookie.</alt></image></fig></section><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">Review</title><p class="- topic/p ">This café has saved me more times than I can count. I am a procrastinator at heart and work best at night but sometimes I get a little too sleepy to finish all my work in time, so I head on over for an oat milk latte pick-me-up. </p></section><section class="- topic/section "><title class="- topic/title ">Recommendation</title><p class="- topic/p ">Since The Coffee Cauldron is known to be a late-night destination, I recommend going as late as you possibly can. Order the fruity coffee flight or a white hot chocolate if you're not a caffeine fan. Have a relaxing conversation with your date and play some cozy video games at their complimentary gaming station.</p><fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">Fruity Coffee Flight at Coffee Cauldron</title><image href="Photos/coffee-cauldron10.jpg" class="- topic/image "><alt class="- topic/alt ">Four coffees titled "raspberry", "peach", "strawberry", and "blackberry"</alt></image></fig></section></body></topic>